A Finding Aid to the Fairfield Porter Papers, 1888-2001 (bulk 1924-1975), in the Archives of American Art AAA.portfair
Archives of American Art
- Artwork, 1918-1975, undated; Series 9; (Boxes 7-10 and 12-17; 2.2 linear feet)
  - Sketchbook, 1957-1958 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Sketchbook, circa 1940-1960 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Sketchbook, circa 1960-1966 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Sketchbooks, circa 1967; (2 volumes in 2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 20-21)
  - Sketchbook, circa 1967-1975 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Sketchbook, circa 1968; (See Box 9, sol) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Sketchbook, circa 1969; (See Box 9, sol) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Sketchbook, circa 1970; (2 volumes in 2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 4-5)
  - Sketchbook, circa 1971; (See Box 9, sol) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Sketchbook, circa 1973; (See Box 9, sol) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Sketchbooks, circa 1974; (3 volumes in 3 folders; see also Box 10, sol) (Box 8, Folder 8-10)
  - Sketchbook, circa 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Sketchbooks, circa 1928-1975; (6 volumes in 6 folders; see also Box 10, sol) (Box 8, Folder 12-17)
  - Sketches and Drawings (Box 8)
    - Childhood Drawings, 1918-1919, undated; (see also Box 10, sol) (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Life Class Sketches, circa 1930-1934; (see Boxes 13 and 14, OV) (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Murals and Frescoes, 1930s; (2 folders including copy negative; see Box 15, OV) (Box 8, Folder 20-21)
    - People, 1933-1947, undated; (3 folders including copies; see also Box 10 (sol) and OV 16) (Box 8, Folder 22-24)
    - Miscellaneous Sketches and Drawings, circa 1920s-1940s; (5 folders including copies) (Box 8, Folder 25-29)
      (Includes sketches from European travels)
    - Miscellaneous Landscapes, undated; (3 folders; see also Box 10 (sol) and OV 17) (Box 8, Folder 30-32)
    - Miscellaneous Painted Sketches, 1938, undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Rebel Arts Illustrations, circa 1934-1935; (See Box 10, sol) (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Prints, circa 1930s; (2 folders, including duplicates; see also Box 12, OV) (Box 8, Folder 35-36)
  - Cartoons, 1975, undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Artwork by Others (Box 8)
    - Print by Peggy Bacon, undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Drawing of Fairfield Porter by Joe Brainard, undated; (See Box 10, sol) (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Drawing by Dick Freeman, undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Drawings by Alex Haberstroh, undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Drawing by Leon Hartl, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Music by Jimmy Lennon, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Childhood Drawings of Johnny Porter, undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Print by Edith Schloss, undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Artist Unknown, 1931, undated; (See also Box 10, sol) (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Oversized Sketchbooks, (See Box 8, folders 2, 3, 6, and 7) (Box 9 (sol))
  - Oversized Sketchbooks, (See Box 8, folders 8, 11, and 12) (Box 10 (sol))
  - Oversized Sketches and Drawings, Childhood Drawings, (See Box 8, folder 18) (Box 10 (sol))
  - Oversized Sketches and Drawings, People, (See Box 8, folder 23) (Box 10 (sol))
  - Oversized Sketches and Drawings, Miscellaneous Landscapes, (See Box 8, folder 32) (Box 10 (sol))
  - Oversized Rebel Arts Illustrations, (See Box 8, folder 34) (Box 10 (sol))
  - Oversized Drawing of Fairfield Porter by Joe Brainard, (See Box 8, folder 39) (Box 10 (sol))
  - Oversized Artwork by Unknown Artist, (See Box 8, folder 46) (Box 10 (sol))
  - Oversized Sketchbook, (see Box 7, folder 1) (Box 12 (OV))
  - Oversized Prints, (See Box 8, folder 35) (Box 12 (OV))
  - Oversized Sketches and Drawings, Life Class Sketches, (See Box 8, folder 19) (Box 13 (OV))
  - Oversized Sketches and Drawings, Life Class Sketches, (See Box 8, folder 19) (Box 14 (OV))
  - Oversized Sketches and Drawings, Murals and Frescoes, (See Box 8, folder 20) (Box 15 (OV))
  - Oversized Sketches and Drawings, People, (See Box 8, folder 23) (Box 16 (OV))
  - Oversized Sketches and Drawings, Miscellaneous Landscapes, (See Box 8, folder 32) (Box 17 (OV))